export const data = [
    {
        question: 'What is version control?',
        answer:'Version control is the practice of tracking and managing changes to software code.',
        url : 'http://guides.beanstalkapp.com/version-control/common-git-commands.html'
    },
    {
        question: 'Git Hooks',
        answer:'Git hooks are scripts that Git executes before or after events such as: commit, push, and receive',
        url : 'https://githooks.com/'
    },
     {
        question: 'What is HTML Tags',
        answer:'HTML tags are like keywords which defines that how web browser will format and display the content. With the help of tags, a web browser can distinguish between an HTML content and a simple content. HTML tags contain three main parts: opening tag, content and closing tag.',
        url : 'https://www.w3schools.com/html/html_attributes.asp'
    },
    {
        question: 'what is HTML Attributes',
        answer:'Attributes provide additional information about elements,attributes usually come in name/value pairs like: name="value"',
        url : 'https://www.w3schools.com/html/html_attributes.asp'
    },
    {
        question: 'What is Data-attribute',
        answer: 'The data-* attribute gives us the ability to embed custom data attributes on all HTML elements.',
        url : 'https://www.w3schools.com/tags/att_data-.asp#:~:text=The%20data%2D*%20attribute%20gives,server%2Dside%20database%20queries'
    },
    {
        question: 'How many HTML elements styling do you know ',
        answer: 'Inline styles - written inside the HTML tags with style attribute ,Internal styles - are between the <style></style> tag, and it is always preferred to place the style tag in the head tag.,External styles – are written in a separate CSS file and need to include the CSS file in the head tag by using a <link>.',
        url : 'https://www.w3schools.com/html/html_styling'
    },
    {
        question: 'Light DOM vs Shadow DOM',
        answer: 'The Shadow DOM is like any other DOM that browsers can generate from HTML code, but the difference is that Shadow DOM serves for encapsulation. It allows a component to have its very own “shadow”  DOM tree, that can’t be accidentally accessed from the main document.',
        url : ''
    },
    {
        question: 'What is block element',
        answer: 'A block element always starts on a new line, and fills up the horizontal space left and right on the web page.  <p>, <div>, <section> …',
        url : 'https://medium.com/@DaphneWatson/css-display-properties-block-inline-and-inline-block-how-to-tell-the-difference-7d3a1e6e3051'
    },
    {
        question: 'What is Inline element',
        answer: 'Inline elements don’t start on a new line, they appear on the same line as the content and tags beside them. <span>, <strong>, <img> … .You can add space to the left and right on an inline element, but you cannot add height to the top or bottom padding or margin of an inline element.',
        url : 'https://medium.com/@DaphneWatson/css-display-properties-block-inline-and-inline-block-how-to-tell-the-difference-7d3a1e6e3051'
    },
    {
        question: 'What is Inline-block',
        answer: 'Inline-block elements are similar to inline elements, except they can have padding and margins added on all four sides.',
        url : 'https://medium.com/@DaphneWatson/css-display-properties-block-inline-and-inline-block-how-to-tell-the-difference-7d3a1e6e3051'
    },
    {
        question: 'What is positon: relative;',
        answer: 'positon: relative; What it really means is “relative to itself”. It limits the scope of absolutely positioned child elements. Any element that is a child of the relatively positioned element can be absolutely positioned within that block.',
        url : 'https://css-tricks.com/absolute-relative-fixed-positioining-how-do-they-differ/'
    },
//    
// 
// 
// 
]
